NOTE-

1. In the login page - 
	1. single click has been simuated as verification of login details
	2. REMEMBER to double click in order to log in. That has been simulated to do so.
	3. I have added a lot of animation. Do see those.
	4. Sorry, but i havent attached my login page and my assignment page.


2. I have intentionally not used bootstrap or MDbootstrap in order to apply the concepts of all bootstrap that i learned. So i used my own CSS to behave it as one. ex- correct usage of vw,vh,%,em,rem,position etc and when to use them. important concepts like flexbox.

i have almost completed building responsive pages. Still was in the designing process but the time wasn't there so much.


3. Tried to fine tune the UI of assignment page. ex-colours,animation,flexbox based event cards.

4. Was not well versed with jQuery. So i used Vanilla JS. sorry about that. In 7 days, i decided to learn JS which i was slightly familiar with earlier. Learning a new language would have crushed me and hindered me in my learning process along with submiting of assignment by the due date. 